talkcharge.com 2019-08-12

# TalkCharge | Privacy Policy

#### General

1\. We at TalkCharge (https://www.talkcharge.com/) are committed to the protection of Information provided by our users to us. You agree to use our services and provides your consent to collect your information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy").

2\. We at TalkCharge (https://www.talkcharge.com/) are committed to the protection of Information provided by our users to us. You agree to use our services and provides your consent to collect your information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy").

#### Information Gathered

1\. Traffic Data Entries

While user visit www.talkcharge.com automatically following entries are been tracked:

  * User IP addresses;
  * User Domain servers;
  * Types of computers by which user is accessing the Website;
  * Types of web browsers used to access the TalkCharge Website;
  * Our Affiliate partner source which may have sent you our Website;

2\. Information Gathered from Users

As our users would be accessing certain pages of the Website, providing access to these areas would require our users to provide with certain Personal Information which includes:

  * Users First and Last name, address, e-mail address & mobile number. Also payment card details if user want to save it for future transactions. Unless asked for KYC which includes DOB and any proof of their identity and/or address that we may request;
  * Transactional Details will be saved of all the transactions been done from TalkCharge account and of the fulfilment of your requests;
  * Users Card details for credit or debit or any other card used for transactions;
  * If any user is participating in any our promotional offers or sponsored offers;
  * If our Users are sending any Correspondence to us;
  * Mobile No. or other details, when we receive a direct Calls from our users looking for support;
  * In case if we are doing Surveys at our website certain details are requested and been uphold with protection;
  * Any Information that is been collected via cookies, that generate while you serve different areas of website.

3\. Legal Obligations

  * To prevent any fraudulent activity and money laundering, we require certain information as per under Legal Obligations. This information might include Third Party Information, any related financial history, at times when we feel it is necessary t or important to minimise our financial risks and prevent any frauds.

#### How Information is used and stored:

1\. TalkCharge uses the gathered information for the following purposes:

  * The information helps us to administer and manage your TalkCharge account.
  * The information allows us to give users access to certain areas of website and provide services that they have requested;
  * The information allows us to give users access to make payments, do recharges, buy Giftcards and make transactions to wallet.
  * The information helps us verify if the user has sufficient funds in their TalkCharge wallet to make payments;
  * The information helps us to send notifications to users about new services and offers;
  * The information might be use to give our development and support team internal training.
  * The information helps us to regulate financial policies, fraudulent activities and security;

2\. TalkCharge retains or store the user information for a minimum period of 5 years after the closure of your users TalkCharge account, which includes the personal data such as user name, contact details, user registered number and transaction history, etc.. Other than this Retained(Stored) Data, we will delete and destroy all Personal Information that we hold about user when he terminates his TalkCharge account. We do not store any online banking login PIN, TAN and/or password.

3\. Please note that TalkCharge will not store user credit card information on closure of account.

#### Information can be Disclosed too:

1\. TalkCharge never discloses any of the user Information to any third parties other than the Website's affiliates, Substantial share holders, the police or other lawful enforcement body, the court if we are under a duty or required by law to disclose or share your personal data, Financial Partners and third parties that you have expressed an interest and lastly the one that referred you to us and we owe a commission to them.

2\. We can use the users Information in aggregate form ensuring no individual user is identified for Marketing, Strategic Development and Audit Purposes.

3\. We also reserve the right to disclose Information if required to do so by law or if we believe that it is necessary to do so to protect and defend the rights, property or personal safety of the Website, or its users.

#### What's Phishing & How it works?

Phishing is the process to attempts to steal personal details and financial account details from a website user. "Phishers" use fake or "spoof" emails to lead users to counterfeit websites where the user is tricked into entering their personal details, such as credit card numbers, user names and passwords. TalkCharge never ask users to disclose any personal or security details by e-mail. If you receive any e-mail supposedly from TalkCharge requesting your personal or security details, please do not respond to it. Please forward any Such E-mail to [Care@TalkCharge.com](mailto:care@talkcharge.com) and thereafter delete the e-mail immediately.

#### Affiliate Channel Related Policies:

1\. We are into affiliates and contain links to and from the websites of our partner stores, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these Stores/merchants, please note that these websites/stores have their own terms of use and privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites. Please also note that the products and services offered on these websites may be limited to persons located or residing in only that particular authority.

2\. Our Android also includes some sharing features, such as the Facebook Like button, or whatsapp, gmail Deals sharing option. These features may collect your IP address, and may set a Cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Website. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

3\. Prior approvals of TalkCharge is mandatory before you create a hyperlink in any form from a third party website to any webpage on the TalkCharge Website. TalkCharge may or may not give such approval at its absolute discretion. In normal circumstances, we may only approve a hyperlink which displays plainly our name or website address. Any use or display of our logos, trade names and trademarks as a hyperlink will not be approved unless in very exceptional circumstances and may be subject to a fee as TalkCharge may determine at its absolute discretion. TalkCharge is not responsible for the setup of any hyperlink from a third party website to any TalkCharge website. Any links so set up shall not constitute any form of co-operation with, or endorsement by, TalkCharge of such third party website. Any link to our website shall always be an active and direct link to our website and shall be made directly to the home or front page of our website only and no "framing" or "deep-linking" of any webpage of our Website or content is allowed. Please contact care@talkcharge.com if you wish to create a hyperlink to any page of our Website on a third party website.

#### User Rights

Our users have the right not to provide us with certain information, which will limit their access to do transaction or go to certain page on website however users can still access to certain pages.

#### Information shared publically:

Any information that users reveal intentionally while reviewing a social media post or commenting on any ongoing online discussion or forum is open to the public and is not in any way private. User should think carefully before disclosing any personally identifiable information in any public forum. What you have written may be seen and/or collected by third parties and may be used by others in ways we are unable to resist or foresee.

#### Amendments to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy so please review it frequently. If we do, then we will notify you here, as well as by posting a notice on our Website and, where appropriate, a link to the modified policy so that you can review it. In all cases, use of information we collect is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected.

#### Restriction of Liability

  * We cannot claim, promise or guarantee about the accuracy, completeness, or adequacy of the contents of this Website and expressly disclaim liability for errors and omissions in the contents of this Website.
  * No warranty of any kind, implied, expressed or statutory, including but not limited to the warranties of non-infringement of third party rights, title, merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose and freedom from computer virus, is given with respect to the contents of the Website or its hyperlinks to other internet resources.
  * Reference in this Website to any specific commercial products, processes, or services, or the use of any trade, firm or corporation name is for the information, affiliate marketing purposes and convenience of the public, and does not constitute endorsement, recommendation, or favouring by us.

If you have questions or concerns, feel free to e-mail us or to correspond at [Care@TalkCharge.com](mailto:care@talkcharge.com) and we will attempt to address your issue.
